AHJEONG SEO

Samsung Research

https://ahjeongseo.github.io

+82 10 7402 9803 ♦ rubyrang2@snu.ac.kr ♦ ahjeong.seo@samsung.com

RESEARCH INTEREST

My primary research goal is to **develop robustly reasoning AI like humans** through structured and disentangled inference. Especially, I'm interested in the explicit and robust reasoning process via traversing over concept graphs constructed with neuro-symbolic approaches. Currently, I have researched improving logical reasoning performances of large-scale models with this method in Samsung Research.

RESEARCH PUBLICATIONS

Neuro-Symbolic Graph Reasoning for Robust Inference in Neural Sequence Models (in preparation)

<u>Ahjeong Seo</u>, Joohyung Lee, *The First Workshop on UM-IoS: Unimodal and Multimodal Induction of Linguistic*<u>Structures (EMNLP 2022 Workshop)</u>

December 2022

Attend What You Need: Motion-Appearance Synergistic Networks for Video Question Answering Ahjeong Seo, Gi-Cheon Kang, Junhan Park, Byoung-Tak Zhang, The Joint Conference of the 59th Annual Meeting of the Association for Computational Linguistics and the 11th International Joint Conference on Natural Language Processing (ACL-IJCNLP 2021)

August 2021

DramaQA: Character-Centered Video Story Understanding with Hierarchical QA

Seongho Choi, Kyoung-Woon On, Yu-Jung Heo, <u>Ahjeong Seo</u>, Youwon Jang, Minsu Lee, Byoung-Tak Zhang, Proceedings of the Thirty-Fifth AAAI Conference on Artificial Intelligence (AAAI 2021) February 2021

Sparse Self-Attention Mechanism for Learning Sequential Video Data

Ahjeong Seo, Kyoung-Woon On, Byoung-Tak Zhang, Korea Software Congress 2019 (KSC 2019) December 2019

WORK EXPERIENCE

AI Methods Team, Samsung Research

Aug. 2021 - Now

Researcher (Adviser: Joohyung Lee)

Seoul. Korea

- · Large-Scale AI: While dealing with large-scale model applications for Samsung's services, I have researched a dual-system model complementing the reasoning limitations of large-scale models with a neuro-symbolic graph approach and plan to submit a paper to the EMNLP 2022 Workshop.
- · Neuro-Symbolic Contents Search: Developed a search engine for movie contents considering both lexical and semantic clues in queries. Specifically, experimented with neural models for semantic search, contributed to a keyword search engine with Elastic Search, and collected and cleaned content data.

RESEARCH PROJECT

Video Turing Test

Sep. 2019 - Aug. 2021

Researcher at Seoul National University (Adviser: Byoung-Tak Zhang)

- · Aiming to build an AI with human-level intelligence for video understanding, conducted research to robustly and explicitly reason via structuring information based on interdisciplinary knowledge. Specifically, based on the human visual information processing process, we proposed a model combining divided visual signals depending on texts for multi-modal reasoning in ACL 2021. Also, based on human cognitive development stages, we suggested DramaQA dataset and a baseline model for hierarchical video understanding in AAAI 2021.
- · Organizing Challenges and Workshops (ECCV 2020, ICCV 2019): Participated in organizing DramaQA challenges and Video Turing Test workshops, managed EvalAI challenge server, and built the homepage: https://dramaqa.snu.ac.kr/

EDUCATION

Seoul National University

Master of Science in NeuroScience

Interdisciplinary Program in Neuroscience (Adviser: Byoung-Tak Zhang)

Thesis: Motion-Appearance Synergistic Networks for Video Question Answering

Hanyang University

Mar. 2014 - Aug. 2019

Sep. 2019 - Aug. 2021

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Engineering

Seoul, Korea

Seoul, Korea

Department of Computer Engineering (minor in Industrial Engineering)

INTERNSHIP

Clova Biz AI, Naver Corp. Apollo Backend, Naver Corp. Nov. 2018 - Feb. 2019

Jul. 2018 - Aug. 2018

Intern Seongnam-si, Korea

· Experimented with ML models depending on the purpose of a service demonstration or a website building project · For research engineering, generated and pre-processed data, built docker environment and APIs, and developed

the website with Spring Framework for backend, and jQuery Ajax, HTML, and CSS for frontend

HONORS AND AWARDS

International Short-Term Dispatch Program Scholarship, Hanyang University

Jun. 2016

Dean's Encouragement Award, Hanyang University

Nov. 2014

Honors Scholarships, Hanyang University

Sep. 2014

EXTRA-CURRICULAR

Algorithm Club at Hanyang University

Mar. 2014 - Aug. 2019

· Participated in algorithm study groups, and received Dean's Encouragement Award in an in-school competition

Hanyang University Buddy Assistants

Jan. - Feb. 2018

Organized and participated in many activities and helped foreign students to adapt to Korean culture and life

Short-term Overseas Dispatch Program, University of Indonesia Exchange Student, Nanyang Technological University Jul. - Aug. 2016 Jan. - May 2016

· Not only took classes but developed cultural competence via activities ranging from field-trip to in-school club

SKILLS AND LANGUAGE

Technical Skills

Pytorch, Tensorflow, Python, C++, C, HTML, R, Java

Language Proficiency Fluent in English and Native in Korean

REFERENCES

Byoung-Tak Zhang

Professor

Department of Computer Science and Engineering, Brain Science, and Cognitive Science

College of Engineering, Seoul National University E-mail: btzhang@bi.snu.ac.kr

https://bi.snu.ac.kr/~btzhang/ Phone: +82 2-880-1833(office), 880-1847(secretary)

Joohyung Lee

Associate Professor / Vice President at Samsung Research

School of Computing, Informatics, and Decision Systems Engineering (CIDSE)

Fulton Schools of Engineering, Arizona State University

AI Methods Team, Samsung Research E-mail: j00hyung.lee@samsung.com

http://peace.eas.asu.edu/joolee/index.html Phone: +82 2-6147-3280

Sanghwa Lee

Research Professor

Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering E-mail: lsh529@snu.ac.kr

College of Engineering, Seoul National University Phone: +82 10-6238-9198